#47 St. Andrews Village, Couva.

Email: karishmabagasar@yahoo.com Tel: 679-6930 / 376-6852

15th July, 2015.

The Human Resource Manager

Dear Sir/ Madam,

The enclosed resume is presented for your consideration regarding the position of Administrative Assistant. I have five (5) years of Administrative Assistant experience, and would like to continue my growth within this field. I am confident I can make a positive contribution to Your Company. I maintain professional and technical knowledge by attending educational workshop; reviewing professional publication; establishing personal networks; participating in professional societies.

I would welcome the opportunity to further discuss this position with you. If you have questions or would like to schedule an interview, please contact me by phone at the above numbers. I have submitted my resume for your review. I look forward to hearing from you.

Yours Respectfully,

Karishma B. Ragoonath. Karishma Bagasar - Ragoonath

#47 St Andrews Village, Couva.

Email: karishmabagasar@yahoo.com Tel: 679-6930 / 376-6852

Objective:

A challenging position in the Administrative Department at a reputed firm, which will allow me to further utilize my existing skills and enable to acquire new abilities.

Skills:

- Planning and Scheduling
- > Remarkable ability to communicate effectively, both orally and in writing
- Customer Service
- > Interdepartmental Coordination
- > Internet Research
- > Telephone Reception
- > Operating all Windows operating system.

Experience:

Administrative Assistant

JEL Enterprises Limited. Val Park Shopping Plaza. Sept 2009 – Oct 2011

- Managed daily schedules, usually for multiple people within the organization. Tasks involved with coordinating company meetings include scheduling and setting up conference rooms, sending reminders and arranging catering.
- Prepared a variety of documents including client proposals, letters and emails in draft and final form utilizing software programs such as Microsoft PowerPoint, Word and Excel. Additionally, I was expected to proofread and edit documents prior to distribution.
- Often utilizes the Internet to gather information to make informed decisions, support initiatives and find solutions.
- Also often maintain and track client accounting and update client contact information.

#47 St Andrews Village, Couva.

Email: karishmabagasar@yahoo.com Tel: 679-6930 / 376-6852

Experience:

Project / HSE Administrative Assistant

United Engineering Services Limited Pt. Lisas Industrial Estate Nov 2012 - Currently

For the Project Manager:

- As the project assistant, I helped in the clarification of the objectives and operations for a particular project or program. This includes handling the logistics of the project--making agendas.
- Also has to attend meetings or programs to take minutes, collect information and prepare correspondence for participants.
- > Conduct extensive research and record data.
- > Acts as a liaison between project directors, coordinators and other staff.
- > Submits monthly budgets for projects and programs in an efficient manner.

For the HSE Manager:

- Managing all documents with respect to the health and safety of employees
- > Reviewing all incident reports, compiling and analyzing monthly statics.
- Providing orientation on HSE to new team mates.
- Assisting in the administration and further development of HSE policy, Manuals, procedures and safe work practices.
- Provide statistical summaries to the health and safety committee and draw attention to significant trends and occurrences.
- Assist in conducting safety training, educational programs and demonstrate the use of safety equipment.
- Inspect specified areas to ensure the presence of the fire prevention equipment, safety equipment and first aid supplies.
- Received and filed all reports of accidents, incidents, near misses and illness.
- In charge of document control to follow suit, the STOW implementation board.

#47 St Andrews Village, Couva

Email: <u>karishmabagasar@yahoo.com</u> Tel: 679-6930 / 376-6852

Education:

Union Claxton Bay Senior Comprehensive (2000-2002) Upper Level Educational Institute (2002-2003)

| CXC O' | Levels | Grade |
|--------|--------------------------|-------|
| 1. | Mathematics | 2 |
| 2. | English Language | 2 |
| 3. | Information Technology | 1 |
| 4. | Principles of Business | 1 |
| 5. | Principles of Accounts | 2 |
| 6. | Human and Social Biology | 2 |
| 7. | Caribbean History | 3 |
| 8. | Integrated Science | 3 |
| 9. | English Literature | 3 |